[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "Why have you given me the big exclusive interview?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "Because when you were on this other show you were (EXPLETIVE DELETED).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "How does that make you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "I'm outraged.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Monday"]}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "When did you hear that Nathan had been killed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "I heard Monday, early afternoon.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nathan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "Let me ask you, Bernadette, as Katie's mother and as the grandmother of these poor young girls now who have no father, what is your reaction as you found out more and more about the background here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Disbelief, I think, because there's so many mistakes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bernadette", "Katie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 101, "question": "Do you have a view about gun control, about background checks, about any of those things that have been so heatedly discussed in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 102, "answer": "I think that they need to be more cautious and I guess look into who purchase these guns.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 126, "question": "Have you been able to explain it at all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 127, "answer": "I haven't went into detail.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Murray"]}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Can you answer that question?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "I don't want Dr. Murray to answer that question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "Can I ask you, do you know -- I mean, do you know the answer to that question?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Who was employing Conrad Murray to be a practitioner for Michael Jackson?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "Well, there's no question in my mind, Piers, that the concert promoter employed Conrad Murray.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray", "Michael Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "It all comes down to him, doesn't it, in the end?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Well, not all of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["AEG"]}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "These are people working for AEG?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "These are people working for AEG, working for him, working for the show.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["AEG"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "How significant will any of that be when this trial starts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "DT", "IN", "DT", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Could be very significant.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "Do you think there's any truth in that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "I really don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "But when you hear Conrad Murray behave like that, that's not the behavior of, as he would pitch himself to us, being a decent, honorable, straightforward physician, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conrad Murray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "Is she going to win, Katherine Jackson on behalf of the family?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "She and the children are going to win, in my opinion.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Katherine Jackson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Who are these school employees who are going to be trusted with being the great defenders against shooters?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "Well, I think first, you look at the recommendations.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. LaPierre", "Asa Hutchinson"]}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Is he -- does he say that schools are gun- free zones or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "Well, I can't speak for Mr. LaPierre, but let me say this about Asa Hutchinson.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "America"]}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", ",", "NN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WRB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "He's not in the gun business?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "Oh, no, wait a second, to fight the background checks, which is where America's come, which is where I told you America would come the last time I was on your program.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 440, "question": "Why are we not having this done in Washington?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 441, "answer": "Well, I mean, it's politics and people want to blame the Republicans.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["September 2014"]}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "And Jay's existing contract, I think, ends in probably September of 2014?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "POS", "VBG", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "September 2014.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["September of 2014"], "PERSON": ["Jay"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "How long do you want it to go on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Let's listen to a bit of this lovely duet last night between these two guys.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Ken, are we buying all this bonhomie between everybody over there now, that it's all one big happy family and the transition has been agreed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "EX", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "No, I don't think it is at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ken"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Conan"]}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "Could he do that, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Well, they decided not to do it when Conan was available.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jay"]}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VB", "RB", "CC", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Ken, would you go to Fox if you were Jay if you were offered it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "If I were Jay, I would take my dignity and leave quietly and count my millions.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jay"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "Bubba, how the devil are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "I'm doing great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "How are you doing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "I'm good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["April 2nd"]}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "Now, is this hovercraft true or is it just an April Fool gag?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "No, it's April 2nd.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["April"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "How are you going to beat him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "Hopefully he gets sick.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "How's it changed your life in the last year?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "First you've got to look at the adoption.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 659, "question": "Any other deeply intimate, personal questions you want to get off your chest (INAUDIBLE)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", ":", "NNP", ":", "."], "aSentId": 660, "answer": "Yes, you know -- yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "-NONE-", "VBP", ":", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "Is it because I'm British?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "No, it's just because you are that (ph).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 678, "question": "What is the point of me interviewing you if all you're going to do is call me that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 679, "answer": "Well, it's not really -- it's not you inviting me back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130402pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 689, "question": "Do you like the celebrity aspect of what you've become since winning the Masters?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 690, "answer": "No, I don't think anybody should like being a celebrity.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]